A Guide to the Melvin E. Steadman collection, 1698-1927
Library of Virginia
- Series I: Local records, 1755-1927., Extent: 10 boxes. (Box 1-10)
  - King and Queen County Recorded Deeds, 1814-1822. (Box 3, Folder 5, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1226)
    Deed between Baylor Temple and Temple Walker (1814).
    Deed between John Walker and Temple Walker (1822).
  - King and Queen County Plats and surveys, 1823. (Box 3, Folder 6, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1226)
    Plat of land of Ann Temple to John Walker.
  - King and Queen County Reconstruction, 1865. (Box 3, Folder 7, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1226)
    Petition of Temple Walker.
  - King George County Plats and Surveys, 1724. (Box 3, Folder 8, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1226)
    Plat of John Scott property.
    Survey of Michael Meldrum land.
  - Loudoun County Agreements, 1779-1899. (Box 3, Folder 9, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1226)
    Agreement between Charles Chinn and Leven Powell (1779).
    Agreement regarding estate of John Elliott (1803).
    Numerous Binns family agreements (1803-1935).
    Agreement between Matthew Davis and Thomas Beech (1840).
    Agreement between Buckner family (1899).
  - Loudoun County Bonds, 1762-1772. (Box 3, Folder 10, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1226)
    Bond of Phillip Counts (1762).
    Bond of Stephen Emory (1762).
    Bond between of Henry O'Daniel (1762).
    Bond of William Fielder and Charles Tyler (1762).
    Bond of Jeremiah Thomas (1762).
    Bond of John King and Joseph Stevens (1762).
    Bond of J. Thomas Sorrell (1762).
    Bond of Caleb Shreve (1763).
    Bond of James Abbott (1764) (not filmed).
    Bond of Joseph Craig (1764).
    Bond of Joseph Stephens (1764).
    Bond of Demse Carroll (1766).
    Bond of Levi Wells and Henry Oxley (1770).
    Bond of William Millan and Simon Triplett (1771).
    Bond of Sampson Trammell (1772).
  - Loudoun County Bonds, 1774-1787. (Box 3, Folder 11, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1226)
    Bond of Thompson Mason, George Johnston, and John Alexander (1774).
    Bond of Sampson Turley (1774).
    Bond of Craven Peyton (1777).
    Bond of Daniel Jennings and Nicholas Minor (1782).
    Bond of Travis and Isaac Wren (1783).
    Bond of William Strother to Stevens Thomson Mason (1783).
    Bond of Adrian Swart (1783).
    Bond of John T. Mason (1783).
    Bond of Solomon and James Nickols (1785).
    Bond of Henry McCabe (1785).
    Bond of Simon Triplett, William Lane, James Lay, and Leven Powell (1786).
    Bond of Adrian and James Swart (1786).
    Bond of Simon Triplett, George Summers, Thomas Lewis, and John Taylor (1786).
    Bond of Nicholas Wyckoff and Adrian Swart (1787).
    Bond of Simon Triplett, Thomas Respess, Thomas Lewis, and James Leith (1787).
    Bond of James Jenkins and Alexander Kidwell (1787).
  - Loudoun County Bonds, 1790-1860. (Box 3, Folder 12, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1226)
    Bond of Godfrey Kiphart (1790).
    Bond of John Reid and John Harriss (1790).
    Bond of Robert Armistead (1789).
    Bond of Francis Berryman and Rebecca Barr (1791).
    Bond of Isaac and Francis Wren (1791).
    Bond of Stacy Hains and George Goff (1793).
    Bond of Isaac and John Wren (1793).
    Bond of Isaac Wren, Daniel Wren, and Peter Urton (1794).
    Bond of Garrott Vanhorn (1794).
    Bond of Abraham B.T. Mason (1794).
    Bond of Amos Fox (1795).
    Bond of James Coleman and Josiah Clapham (1795).
    Bond of Abraham B. T. Mason (1797).
    Bond of Amox Fox and James Davis (1798).
    Bond of Bonham Divine and David Miller (1798).
    Bond of John Thornton and Joseph Lewis (1798).
    Bond of Darling Ball (1798).
    Bond of Thomas Wren and Joseph Lewis (1802).
    Bond of John, Richard, and William Presgraves (1802).
    Bond of Thomas and Alexander Thornton and Frederick Slaughter (1803).
    Bond of John Bogue and William Redwood (1803).
    Bond of John and Garrett Hough and James Curtis (1807).
    Bond of Charles Binns and Hugh Douglas (1813).
    Bond regarding estate of John Binns (1814).
    Bond of Edward Dulin (1822).
    Bond of Henry H. Hamilton (1822).
    Bond of John Janney (1831).
    Bond of John Hardy (1839).
    Bond of Stevens T. Mason (1845).
    Bond of Jacob Waltman (1846).
    Bond of James Wrenn Jr. and Sr. (1860).
  - Loudoun County Clerks Records, nd. (Box 3, Folder 13, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1226)
    Receipt of Tankerville.
  - Loudoun County Church Records, 1785. (Box 3, Folder 14, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1226)
    Petition from Baptist Church of Little River.
  - Loudoun County Church Records, 1785. (Box 3, Folder 15, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1226)
    Inventory of property belonging to Shelburne Parish.
  - Loudoun County County Court, 1757-1767. (Box 3, Folder 16, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1226)
    Wrenn vs. Sanford (nd).
    Gist vs. Binns (nd).
    Violet vs. Trammell (1757).
    Hamilton vs. Lynham (1758).
    Cockerill vs. James (1759).
    Eaton vs. Delasmeti (1760).
    Marthos vs. Davis (1761).
    Hicks vs. Jenkins (1762).
    Janney vs. Black (1763).
    King George III vs. Samuel Jenkins and Silvanus Lay (1763)
    Copy of inventory of Nicholas Seward's estate (1763).
    John Ingerness vs. Richard Coombs (1764).
    Delashmutt vs. Vansandt (1764).
    Delashmutt vs. McKenzey (1766).
    Lane vs. French (1764).
    Lucket vs. French (1764).
    French vs. Mitinger (1767).
    Moses Hall vs. Alexander Henderson (1767).
  - Loudoun County County Court, 1768-1789. (Box 3, Folder 17, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1226)
    Boggess vs. Dawkins (1768).
    Orr vs. Cockerill (1770).
    Osborn vs. French (1770).
    French vs. Hanks (1771).
    Plumer etc vs. Hanks (1771).
    Spiers etc vs. Hanks (1771).
    Hamilton vs. Shilling (1772).
    King George III vs. John and Amos Jenkins (1772).
    Boone vs. Oxley (1773).
    Sebastian's Administrator vs. Trammell (1773).
    Trammell vs. Gunnell (1773).
    Jenkins vs. Riley (1774).
    Cavan vs. Carr (1784).
    French vs. Jefferson (1784).
    Wildman vs. Hague (1784).
    Doughty vs. Henry Jr. (1784).
    Sutton vs. Canby and Hough (1784)--located misc. reel 1226 after Wrenn vs. Sanford (nd).
    Carr vs. Mason (1786).
    Williams vs. Wrenn (1786).
    Binns vs. Alexander (1787).
    Sanford Administrator vs. Mahonner (1783).
    Watson vs. Wren (1787).
    Bill of sale Smith to Love (1788).
    Dennis vs. French (1789).
    Whitacre vs. Palmer (1789).
  - Loudoun County County Court, 1790-1795. (Box 3, Folder 18, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1227)
    Doughty vs. Kellison (1790)--listed as Doughty vs. Hellison on reel.
    Doughty vs. Callister (1790).
    Palmer vs. Whitaker (1790).
    French vs. Hutchison (1791).
    Littleton vs. Minor (1791).
    Chelton vs. Price (1792).
    Janney vs. Emery (1792).
    Dowdall vs. Keith (1792).
    King vs. Price (1792).
    Williams vs. Jenkins (1792).
    Mason vs. Doughty and Fouch (1792).
    French vs. Hugh (1794).
    John Littlejohn, assignee of Robert Henwood, vs. Brashears (1794).
    Selden vs. Fouch (1794).
    Ashford vs. McDaniel (1795).
    Carr, assignee of John Downs, vs. Daily (1795).
    McDaniel vs. Cocke's Executor (1795).
    Smarr vs. Moore (1795).
    Stuart and Love vs. Jenkins (1795).
    .
  - Loudoun County County Court, 1796-1807. (Box 3a, Folder 1, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1227)
    Henwood vs. Doughty (1796).
    Holling vs. Russell (1796).
    Selden vs. Fouch (1796).
    Swaney vs. West (1797) [includes will of William West, information on Lewis Ellzey, and case regarding the freedom of Simon Swaney].
    Lewis vs. French Jr. (1798).
    Rollins vs. Brashears (1799).
    Gryme's vs. Jenkins (1800).
    Wrenn vs. Harris (1803).
    Wrenn vs. Vanloper (1805).
    Bringle vs. Divine (1806).
    Wood vs. Wrenn (Craig's assignee vs. Wrenn) (1806).
    Bogue vs. Rawlings (1807).
  - Loudoun County County Court, 1808-1822. (Box 3a, Folder 2, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1227)
    Wrenn vs. Mershon (1808).
    Binder vs. Bradshaw (1809).
    Chamberlain vs. French (Gallagher's assignee vs. French)(1809).
    Todhunter vs. Gover (1810).
    Bannatine vs. Peyton (1812).
    French vs. French and Lunsford (French's administrator vs. French, etc.)(1812).
    French vs. Lewis etc. (1812).
    French vs. Violett (1812).
    Botton vs. Binns (1814).
    Braden vs. Binns (1814).
    Balch vs. Binns (1814).
    Binns vs. Binns (1815)--located on misc. reel 1226 after Payne vs. Carter (At and Va Tier vs. Carter).
    Garner vs. Binns (1816).
    Talbott vs. Divine (1817).
    French vs. Lewis (Adams, assignee vs. Lewis) (1819).
    Berry vs. French (1819).
    McDaniel vs. McPherson (1819).
    Binns vs. Fling (1821).
    French and Silcote vs. Violett (1821).
    Johnston vs. French (1822).
    Masons vs. Crowe (1822).
  - Loudoun County, 1823-1886. (Box 3a, Folder 3, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1227)
    Binns vs. Saunders (1823).
    Schroeder vs. Bennett and Lee (1824).
    Mutual Assurance Society vs. Gibson (1825).
    Mutual Assurance Society vs. Lacey (1825).
    Mutual Assurance Society vs. Sappington (1825).
    Mutual Assurance Society vs. Vandeventer (1825).
    Smith vs. French (1825).
    Violett vs. French.
    French vs. Woody (1827).
    Governor Giles vs. Bennett (1828).
    Whaley vs. Darne (1832).
    Caylor vs. Jenkins (1834).
    Grubb vs. Mabberly (1860).
    Fitzhugh vs. Frazier (1866)--located on misc. reel 1226 after Gist vs. Binns.
    Barrett vs. French (1866).
    French and Beans vs. Minor (1867).
    Payne vs. Carter (At and Va Tier Company vs. Carter) (1886)--located on misc. reel 1226 after Fitzhugh vs. Frazier.
  - Loudoun County Court of Chancery, 1772-1807. (Box 3a, Folder 4, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1228)
    Rozell vs. Moreland (1772).
    West vs. West (1772).
    Turley vs. Cleveland (1790).
    Brown vs. Arnett (1791).
    Bryan Fairfax vs. Henry Lee (1794).
    Hanks vs. French (1794).
    Halling vs. Coleman (1795).
    Abricks vs. Emrey (1800).
    Wrenn vs. Harriman (1803).
    James vs. Botts (1804).
    Douglas vs. Tibbs (1807).
  - Loudoun County Court of Chancery, 1812-1832. (Box 4, Folder 1, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1228)
    Jenkins vs. Jenkins (1812).
    Lovett vs. Ellzey (1812).
    French vs. French (1817).
    Mason vs. Sanders (1827).
    Henry vs. French (1832).
    McPherson vs. Thrift (1832).
    Berkley vs. Brett (nd)--located first on misc. reel 1228.
    Johnson vs. Garrison (nd)--located second on misc reel 1228.
    Booth vs. Booth (nd)--located third on misc. reel 1228.
  - Loudoun County Court of Chancery, 1806. (Box 4, Folder 2, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1228)
    John Alexander Binns vs. Alexander Waugh.
  - Loudoun County District Court, 1790. (Box 4, Folder 3, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1228)
    John Orr vs. William Mitchell.
  - Loudoun County District Court, 1809. (Box 4, Folder 4, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1228)
    John Sutton vs. Bernard Hough.
  - Loudoun County Superior Court of Law and Chancery, 1808-1831. (Box 4, Folder 5, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1228)
    Russell vs. Lee (1810).
    Commonwealth vs. Talbott (1812).
    McDaniel vs. Alder (1813).
    Carr vs. Bogue (1815).
    Binns vs. Harding (1816).
    Waugh vs. Binns (1817).
    Gist vs. Binns (1820).
    Richards vs. Lane (1820) [see Kearlsey Mines Correspondence].
    Moreland vs. Houghs (1823).
    Sanders vs. Binns (1823).
    Commonwealth vs. Dulaney (1829).
    Murrey vs. Binns (1826).
  - Loudoun County Superior Court of Law and Chancery, 1833-1847. (Box 4, Folder 6, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1229)
    Waltman vs. Waltman (1833).
    Rathie vs. Gassaway (1834).
    Catlett vs. Belt (1841).
    Commonwealth vs. Ephriam (slave of Joshua Hutchison) and Sophia (slave of Mary Hutchison) (1845) [case of poisoning].
    Charlotte E. Mason estate (1847).
    Arundle vs. Saffer (nd).
  - Loudoun County Superior Court of Law and Chancery, 1834. (Box 4, Folder 7, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1229)
    George W. Chalmers vs. George Tavener.
  - Loudoun County Circuit Court, 1855-1887. (Box 4, Folder 8, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1229)
    Mount vs. Fitzhugh (1855).
    American Drier Co. vs. Bowie (1887).
  - Loudoun County Circuit Court, 1872. (Box 4, Folder 9, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1229)
    James M. Wallace vs. Charles E. Evard.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book A, 1757-1812. (Box 5, Folder 1, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1229)
    Deed between William Shreve and David Carroll (1757).
    Deed between John Berkley and Charles Tyler (1757).
    Deed between Bernard Young and Isaac Nichols (1758).
    Deed between Sam Aubrey and Matthew Gossett (1758).
    Power of attorney of William Spencer (1758).
    Deed between John Wren and Francis Harryman (1795).
    Deed between John Wren and Thomas Ludwell Lee (1796).
    Deed between Edmund Lee and John Dulin (1809).
    Deed between Elisha Janney and James Keith (1813)--not on misc. reel.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book A#2, 1794-1801. (Box 5, Folder 2, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1229)
    Deed between Charles Dulin and Leven Powell (1794).
    Deed between Jeremiah Reinker and William Halling (1801)--not on misc. reel.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book A#3, 1814. (Box 5, Folder 3, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1229)
    Deed between John Mathias and Richard Henderson.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book A#4, 1837. (Box 5, Folder 4, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1229)
    Deed between Samuel Hoffman and Elizabeth Hoffman.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book B, 1760-1761. (Box 5, Folder 5, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1229)
    Deed between Catesby Cooke and John Trammell (1760), 2 copies.
    Deed between Thomas Hail and William West (1760).
    Deed between Catesby Cocke and William Holmes (1760).
    Deed between Nicholas Minor and John Hereford (1761).
    Deed between Ann Janney and William Rust (1761).
    Deed between Francis Elgin and Robert Adam (1761), 2 copies.
    Deed between John Hanby and John Trammell (1761), 2 copies.
    Deed between Margaret Sinclear and John Trammell (1761).
    Deed between Thomas Hale and William West (1761).
    Deed between John Carlisle and John Clapham (1761).
    Deed between John Carlisle and William Hurley (1761).
    Deed between Samuel Grigsby and James Lane (1761).
  - Loudoun County Deed Book C, 1762. (Box 5, Folder 6, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1229)
    Deed between John Hereford and John Vessells (1762).
    Deed between Peter Chapman and James Lane (1762).
    Deed between Charles Benson and William Trammell (1762).
    Deed between John Patterson and William Henderson (1762).
    Deed between Lord Fairfax and Jonathan Mires (1762).
    Deed between James Vessells and Christopher Perfect (1762).
  - Loudoun County Deed Book C#2, 1803. (Box 5, Folder 7, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1229)
    Deed between Edmund J. Lee and Stephen Cooke.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book C#5, 1850. (Box 5, Folder 7a)
    Deed between George Beatty and Sarah Jane Hardin
  - Loudoun County Deed Book D, 1755-1765. (Box 5, Folder 8, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1229)
    Deed between William Harle (executors) and Lee Massory (1755).
    Deed between Edward Snickers and John Davis (1763).
    Deed between George Forester and Joseph Hutchinson (1763), 2 copies.
    Deed between Joseph Holtzelan and Minor Winn (1763), 2 copies.
    Deed between Jacob Reamey and John Pryor (1763).
    Deed between Alexander Arnett and Samuel Arnett (1765).
    Deed between Sarah Servis and John Trammell (1765).
    Deed between Samuel Oldham and Francis Summers (1763).
    Deed between Richard Nelson and Edward Garrat (1763).
    Deed between James Donaldson and Hunter Campbell (1763).
    Deed between Barnaby Egan and John Ballendine (1764), 2 copies.
    Deed between Thomas Aubrey and George Lutwig (1764).
    Deed between Solomon Hoge and John Jones (1764).
    Deed between Sampson Turley and Harris (1764).
    Deed between John Hart and William Trammell (1765).
    Deed between Samuel Johnston and Samuel Compton (1765).
    Deed between Frederick Nicholas and Jonathan Pike (1765).
    Deed between John Heart and William Trammell (1765).
    Deed between Walter Williams and Simon Triplett (1765), 2 copies.
    Deed between Daniel Lawrence and Christopher Lownes (1765).
    Deed between John Trammell and William Trammell (1765).
  - Loudoun County Deed Book D#2, 1803. (Box 5, Folder 9, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1229)
    Deed between Mary Armistead to Elizabeth Armistead.
    Deed between Ferdinand Fairfax and Joseph Lewis.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book D#5, 1850. (Box 5, Folder 10, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1229)
    Deed between Joseph Arandell and John Janey.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book D#7, 1890. (Box 5, Folder 11, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1229)
    Deed between John H. Nelson and Peter Poland.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book E, 1766. (Box 5, Folder 12, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1229)
    Deed between Craven Peyton and Locham and Gilpin.
    Deed between William Cline and William Ellsey.
    Deed between Daniel James and Cravey Peyton.
    Power of attorney of Thomas Colville.
    Deed between Robert Peyton and Craven Peyton (2 copies).
    Deed between Thomas Aubrey and John Gibson.
    Deed between Richard Coombs and Jacob Shilling.
    Deed between John Patterson and James Brown.
    Deed between Thomas Pritchard and Michael Kortz.
    Deed between James Ingles and John Linson.
    Deed between Walter Middleton and Humphrey Peake.
    Power of attorney of John Edmonson.
    Deed between Thomas Phillips and Jonas Potts.
    Power of attorney of John Moore.
    Power of attorney of Samuel Mead.
    Deed between Thomas Lewis and John Goss.
    Deed between Charles Tyler and James Nisbett.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book E#2, 1804. (Box 5, Folder 13, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1229)
    Deed between Leven Powell and Richard Bland Lee.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book E#8, 1907. (Box 5, Folder 14, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1229)
    Deed between Rachel A. Paxton and Samuel T. Hickman.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book F, 1746-1786. (Box 5, Folder 15, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1229)
    Deed between Thomas Lord Fairfax and William Shreve (1746).
    Deed between Spencer Grayson and Hector Ross (1767), 2 copies.
    Deed between John Harle and Samuel Trammell (1767), 2 copies.
    Deed between Jacob Ramey to Jemime Vilet (1767).
    Deed between William Cummins and Fleming Patterson (1767).
    Deed between William Barr and Charles Pressley (1767).
    Deed between William Dodd and John Dodd (1767).
    Deed between William Davis and Richard Davis (1768).
    Deed between Thomas Stone and Benjamin Mason (1768).
    Deed between Nicholas Minor and Spence Minor (1768).
    Deed between John Dodd and Jacob Janney (1773), 2 copies.
    Deed between Robert Burwell and James Coleman (1773).
    Deed between Joseph Arthur and Philip Noland (1773).
    Deed between Robert Burwell and Josiah Clapham (1773).
    Deed between Thomas Lewis and Samuel Love (1786).
  - Loudoun County Deed Book F#3, 1822. (Box 5, Folder 16, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1230)
    Deed between George Tanner and Jonathan Carter.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book F#5, 1852. (Box 5, Folder 17, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1230)
    Deed between Fanny Lee and others and H. J. Harrison and John Janney.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book G, 1768-1770. (Box 5, Folder 18, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1230)
    Deed between Francis Heronomus and John Rector (1768).
    Deed between Charles Eskridge and Francis Dade (1768).
    Deed between Richard Stewart and Richard Coombs (1769).
    Deed between Jacob Shilling and Joseph Stephens (1769).
    Deed between Joshau Gore and James Dillon (1769), 2 copies.
    Deed between John Shepherd and William Douglas (1769).
    Deed between James Brown and Milly Brown (1769).
    Deed between Robert Stephens and Ann Onsley (1769).
    Deed between William West and Benjamin Hutchinson etc. (1769).
    Deed between Jacob Smith and Ester Wills and Landon Carter (1769), 2 copies.
    Deed between Thomas John and Leonard Helm (1769).
    Deed between Jacob Smith and Landon Carter (1769).
    Deed between Henry Talbot etc. and James Whaley and Richard Stephens (1770).
  - Loudoun County Deed Book G#2, 1806. (Box 5, Folder 19, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1230)
    Deed between John Surghnor and Aron Devine.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book G#3, 1823. (Box 5, Folder 20, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1230)
    Deed between Bushrod Washington and William Reeder etc.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book G#5, 1853. (Box 5, Folder 21, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1230)
    Deed between Jane McCabe and Matthew Harrison.
    Deed between Samuel Caldwell and Joseph Hilliard.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book H, 1770-1772. (Box 5, Folder 22, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1230)
    Deed between Edward Thompson and Jesse Woodard (1770).
    Deed between William Pearle and Nicholas Wyckoff (1770).
    Deed between Daniel Peake and Amos Davis (1770).
    Deed between Joseph Stephens and Alexander McIntire (1770).
    Power of attorney of Benjamin Hiatt (1771).
    Deed between William Thomas and Joshua Evans (1771).
    Deed between Thomas Shepard and William Neilson (1771).
    Deed between John Ballindine and Thomas Drake (1771).
    Deed between Joseph Stephens and Smith King and James Whaley (1771).
    Deed between William Muirhead and William Neale (1771).
    Deed between James Ramsay and Joshua Evans (1771).
    Deed between Michael Kortz and Henry Harris(1771).
    Deed between Reubin Doughty and Jenkins Phillips (1771).
    Deed to examine lands of Mrs. Hough (1772).
    Deed between Thomas Shepard and William Neilson (1772), 2 copies.
    Deed between William Noddy and Thompson Mason (1772).
  - Loudoun County Deed Book H#3, 1825. (Box 5, Folder 23, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1230)
    Deed between Samuel Murrey and George Richards.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book H#5, 1853. (Box 5, Folder 24, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1230)
    Deed between Matthew Hammerley and Gen. George Rush.
    Deed between M. P. Cochran and trustees of the Baptist Congregation at Waterford.
    Deed between George Beatty and John W. Gover.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book H#6, 1875. (Box 5, Folder 25, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1230)
    Deed between Robert Poland and William Poland.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book I, 1772. (Box 5, Folder 26, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1230)
    Deed between James Lane and John McCowan.
    Deed between James Ross and James Mason.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book J#2, 1807. (Box 5, Folder 27, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1230)
    Deed between Thomas Triplett and William Mason.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book J#5, 1854. (Box 5, Folder 28, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1230)
    Deed between George Beamer and trustees of Catoctin School House.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book K, 1773-1775. (Box 5, Folder 29, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1230)
    Deed between Henry Oxley and Farling Ball (1773).
    Deed between George W. Fairfax and Bryan Fairfax and Hannah Washington (1773), 2 copies.
    Deed between George W. Fairfax and John Carlyle (1773).
    Deed between Joseph Hough and John Hough (1773).
    Deed between James Kennady and Joseph Janney (1773), 2 copies.
    Deed between Gabriel Fox and Amox Fox (1774).
    Deed between Mahlan Janney and William Beens (1774).
    Deed between John Neale and Leven Powell and Peyton Harrison (1774).
    Deed between Daniel Barnes and Edward Snickers (1774).
    Deed between James Kennady and Joseph Janney (1774).
    Deed between John Stallop and Edward Snickers (1774).
    Power of attorney of Charles Morris (1774).
    Deed between Robert Jamisson and John Vestall (1773).
    Power of attorney of John Head (1774).
    Deed between William Court and Jeremiah Cockerill (1774).
    Deed between William Davis and Presley Davis (1774), 2 copies.
    Deed between Samuel Cox and Amos Thompson (1774).
    Deed between Amos Fox and Gabriel Fox (1774).
    Power of attorney of Thomas Usher (1774).
    Power of attorney of Mahlon Taylor (1774).
    Deed between John Berkley and John Linton (1775).
    Deed between Samuel Smith and Simon Hancock (1775).